Or the major meeting of the Miami Statue Utility Authority for today's date and time.
I am too, as in the occasion by Pastor of 1st Ann Smith, his church, Todd Bowman.
Todd, thanks for joining us again tonight.
That's great.
Gracious in life, affirming God, we gather here this evening, and we meet in order to serve the
citizens of this great city.
We pray that you would be present, and that you would help us to continue to use the resources,
that you have blessed us with wisely.
We seek and strive to represent all members of this community fairly, make decisions that will
promote the common good.
We recognize our responsibility and not only to the past and to the present, but also towards
the future.
Help us to be better servants, stewards, and caretakers of all that you entrust to us.
We'll continue to give you thanks for the police officers, the firefighters, the first responders
among us.
Who put themselves in harm's way in order to protect us and our families.
May you bless them in their loved ones.
Bless the business of this meeting and the deliberations and conversations that go into it.
Release us from our fears, our worries, our anxieties.
Help all of us to be open to hear one another's ideas and beliefs.
Help us to be respectful of our differences.
Help us to grow in our wisdom and understanding of each other in ourselves.
Help us to focus on those things that unite us and bring us together,
finding common ground and a shared purpose.
Help us to be forced as for positive change and good.
All of this we pray in your name and in your power.
Please join in the pledge.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America and to the Republic for which it stands.
All in nation under God, indivisible with liberty and justice.
Thank you.
Thanks again, God.
Item five is, excuse me, Adam four is a public input and unscheduled personal period.
Is anyone in the audience wish to address the council?
Item five is Consentant Gender, Stam is recommending item six through 11 for the consent agenda.
If there are no questions on any of those items that entertain a motion to approve as recommended.
So moved.
And a second please.
Well call.
Lewis, I work it.
I.
West Coast.
So.
All right, it takes us to item 12, which is except a reject big number.
C-1926 and amount of 328,000 to C-mins industry for substation,
bikers and approve the contract contingent upon the submission of required documents and also
authorized city manager has designated side notice.
Pushing.
All right, this is the, um, the breakers we talked about at the last meeting, and we got.
on became under Olsen's estimate, so we thought we'd be asking the council to accept
this bid so we can be forward. This is a record for a resup one and some two
subsup one is their the operations and our sub two is a nickel
substation. Todd, do you remember what the Olsen's estimate was?
Yes, approximately. It was around 390, 360, 360, 360, and our bid came in
at 228,000. Great. In any questions on the bid documents or
staff's recommendation, do we have a motion to accept bid C-1926 and then
our 32809 and approve the contract contingent submission of the documents
and approve the city manager or his designated to sign those to proceed.
I'll make a motion. And a second?
Second.
Roll call please.
What's the list? I work it.
I'm 13 and accept a reject bid C-1937 for 13.2 kb, a kb, a sub station expansion
for sub station and C-1938 for the expansion of a sub station too, shall?
So, that recommendation on this is the reject bid.
We've only got the Q-Bids for it. Both of them exceeded estimate.
There was a lot of things working against this one. Some of them were buying an holiday
because we started about four. Still getting 21 days. They said one at a time.
They had a lot of bids do it the same time, so we're recommending reject.
We've actually got it in paper today.
Both of them also had the same sub contract.
They had the same sub or cyborg, which was quite a bit over estimate.
I think going back down we can get some better numbers.
And there's still some time. So, we just got to us a little bit.
What's a method of locating the people that are going to be doing this?
It's a very specialized skill set.
We reached out. We reached out to people that we worked with.
I was reached out. We reached out. We have it on a plan room that's a nationwide publication.
So, it's gone national.
Do they?
It's all from everywhere.
I had a call from Canada.
From Canada.
No questions.
And everywhere. But we got two bids.
We had one company said, we were there.
This is perfect. This is what we do.
But we worked for Liberty all the time.
The two subsations also do the same day.
We said we do stuff with them every year.
So, we really know if it's you guys.
We had a big one to get our bid in.
We could get in for Liberty.
So, that's what I understand.
So, they may be interested in that.
Yes, they may be interested in that.
I had to cut one project out.
And he said, the one that I worked for all the time.
You know, obviously one out.
So, I think we can get more bids.
We're going to give them some, they've got a few extra days now between all the days, between now and by an open, so we're not opening on the Tuesday, we're opening on the Thursday, so that gets them free business days to get by home numbers together.
Contractors have to wait till the last minute, we'll miss that together.
And you still feel like we're on schedule?
Yes.
We will have to talk to the transformer contractor about storage for the units that we don't want here until the past.
That's a great form.
We'll be in another moment of storage.
Any other questions?
Do we have a motion then to...
Vandality to reject these individually, probably?
I know they're both listed.
But let's just do it that way.
We have a motion to reject that C19-37.
And I'll second that roll call, please.
Or can?
Should we?
Hi.
Do we have a question?
Do we have a motion to reject the C19-38?
Make a motion.
And...
I'll second it.
Will call, please.
Hi.
Any new business anyone?
Any trustee community announcements?
I don't know.
We have a motion to adjourn.
Second.
Roll call, please.
Question.